

# NAUSHIKHA JAYAWICKRAMA

**Phone**: +94 76331 6991

E-mail: hello@naushikha.com

Website: naushikha.com

#### **COMPUTER ENTHUSIAST**

## PROFIL F

Hardworking, self-motivated ambitious programmer with a keen eye for detail. Excellent track record of performance in all tasks undertaken with nearly 3 years of cumulative industrial working experience in fields such as game testing, networking, customer support and tutoring.

Aiming to work in a challenging but friendly environment with a goal to become a part of a team.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### PLAYTESTER

#### Arimac (Jan 2021 - May 2021)

• Testing and evaluating Android mobile games

#### VIRTUAL INTERN

#### Nestlé (Oct 2020 - Dec 2020)

Researching for the supply-chain division to localize use of raw materials

#### SYSTEM ENGINEER

#### Telasis Solutions (2017 - 2019)

- System and network installation and administration
- Server and desktop hardware configuration

#### VIRTUAL ASSISTANT

#### Voigue (Dec 2017 - Jan 2018)

 Support team services to handle Daraz.lk's excess user traffic during Christmas

#### INTERN

#### Third Space Global (Dec 2016 - Jan 2017)

• Online tutoring mathematics for school children stationed in the UK

## SKILLS

- Linux, networking and system administration
- WebGL graphics and web design
- Hardware installation, upgrading and maintennance
- Quick learning
- Problem solving
- Adaptability
- Fluent communication

## **EDUCATION**

## BSC (HONS) COMPUTER SCIENCE

#### University of Colombo School of Computing (2019 >> )

• Current GPA: 3.8

### 0/L, A/L

#### Ananda College, Colombo 10. (2003 - 2016)

• Ordinary Level : 9 As

• Advanced Level: Z-Score - 2.3634, Island Rank - 8, District Rank - 2





